

INFORMATION

0

Di An city, Binh Duong, Viet Nam

SKILLS

ANALYSIC AND DESIGN APPLICATION **SYSTEM**

I have more than 10 years experience in Software Developer role. I am working as a software analyst and designer, Then, I get requests from clients to analyze, clarify, and detail by document. Finally, I make software design document with high and detail level.

HEAD/LEAD PROJECTS

I have more than 5 years experience in Head/Lead Projects role. I am working as a PM with Waterfall and Agile process.

TRAINGING, LECTURING, COACHING Training about Software system process for customers.

Lecturing in academy, university, ...

APPLY BUSINESS IN DEVELOP SOFTWARE

I have more 5 year experience working in retail, so I undersand about CRM/CLM business and do better.

DEVELOPING ADVANCED FEATURES

Beside working management role, I also develop anvanced features as payment integartion, firebase notification integartion, email authencation integartion, google services integartion, media management, image analyst process, ..

NGUYEN KIM THUAN

SENIOR DEVELOPER, HEAD/LEAD PROJECT, CTO, **LECTURER**

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am always self-study to improve professional qualifications and management capacity to response all customer requirements.

I am working hard to make product with service mindset, understanding requiremnets of customers to help them have a good experience.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER // 01/2013 - 06/2016

Fsoft Ho Chi Minh Co., Ltd

Coding, testing with UT, IT, ST

Program language:

- + Web base: HTML, JS, JQuery, ...
- + C++: Command line, Library, ...
- + C#: Winform, Console, MVC, ...
- +Java: JSP, Spring FW, ...

SQL: MS SQL, My SQL, Oracle SQL, Postgre SQL, ...

SENIOR DEVELOPER, HEAD PROJECT // 07/2016 - now

MS Apptech Co., Ltd

Design, Document writing, Coding Difi cult Features, Integrating, Revieving, Training, ... Program language:

- + Web base: HTML, JS, JQuery, Node JS, ...
- + C++: Command line, Library, ...
- + C#: Winform, Console, MVC, API, .NET Core, WCF, Service, ...
- +Java: Swing App, JSP, Spring FW, ...
- + SQL: MS SQL, My SQL, Oracle SQL, Postgre SQL, ...
- + No SQL: MongoDB

😑 MENTOR & COACH // 06/2016 - 06/2022

FUNIX

Mentoring, coaching, exam question, ...

😑 LECTURER // 08/2022 - now

FPT Aptech, FPT University

Lecturing, coaching, exam question, ...

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE // 10/2008 - 10/2012

Ho Chi Minh city open university

UNIVERSITY LECTURER CERTIFICATE // 09/2022 - 11/2022

National Academy of Education Management

TYPICAL PROJECTS

HOBBIES

Traveling, Relaxing, Walking, Running, Footbal, ..

MORE

Salary:

- + Full-time: 50 milion VNÐ/ month
- + Part-time: 250.000 VNÐ/hour



CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIP/LOYALTY MANAGER (CRM / CLM)

// 10/2020 - 12/2021, 05/2022 - now

MALL, MART, SUPERMARTKET, COFFEE STORE, DEPARTMENT STORE, ...

Project size: 20 - 40

Position Senior Developer, Head Project

Desing, Document writing, Coding dificult features, Integrating, Reviewing, Training, ...

Structure projects

IOS Customer App, Android Customer App, Web Customer App, Web Api Service, WCF Service, Win app service, Win app console service, Web app admin, Web app CS, Win app admin, Payment Integration, Firebase notification Integration, Social Network Integration, Company Email Integration, ...